http://www.toolexperts.com/tool-experts-privacy-policy.html

Last added items
Subtotal:
Corona Virus News
Delays with orders and shipping due to Corona Virus.
04/08/2020
Become A Tool Experts Member
Tool Experts Members save on some of our most popular products with prices so low we are not allowed to advertise them.
01/23/2020
It's Home Inspection Time!
This Deluxe Home Inspection Tool Kit - Perfect Kit For Home Inspectors Who Want The Best Tools, Most Features, To Do The Job Fast & Right.
12/23/2019
Cable Ferret Camera Combo
- Includes a Ferret Stick Extension Pole!!
Get Yours Today!
10/31/2019
Warming Products
Keep Caulk, Paint Can, Propane Tanks and More Warm in Cold Weather
All news
Privacy Policy
At Tool Experts.com we understand the importance of securing your personal information. In that regard, we make every effort to protect the information that you provide us. Your information will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy. The information you provide us is used to process orders that you place on our website including name, address, email address and credit card information. Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to help you make informed decisions when using our web site and all of our related services therein.Contact InformationTo request a correction or deletion of your private information, or if you have any questions and general comments about this privacy policy, please contact us: info@toolexperts.com. Mailing address: Tool Experts, 438 Old Hwy 70, Harriman, TN 37748 (865) 882-3833What Information Do We Collect?When visiting the our web site, you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you voluntarily choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information gathered on a collective basis as you and others browse our Web site.Registration Information You will provide us information about yourself and your firm or company when purchase items from us, register for certain services, or request catalog.How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us? Generally, we use personal information for purposes of filling orders, providing customer service, managing and expanding our business activities, and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable.Email InformationIf you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. If you use our "Email this page" feature to send a copy of that page to someone else, your email address will appear as the sender of the email. We do not have the ability to collect this information.Choice/Opt-outIf you do not wish to receive any promotional or marketing e-mails and/or surface mail catalog, you may opt-out of receiving those communications by sending an e-mail with the subject line "Unsubscribe" to unsubscribe@toolexperts.com.What Are Cookies?A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?As you visit our Web site, the site uses its cookies to differentiate you from other customers.Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies.Sharing Information with Third PartiesWe may enter into alliances, partnerships or other business arrangements with third parties who may be given access to your name and address for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that we think will be of interest to you. We do not share your email address with third partiesWe also use third parties to process credit card payments. In connection with these offerings and business operations, our partners and other third parties may have access to your personal information for use in connection with business activities.How Do We Protect Your Information?Secure Information TransmissionsEmail is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. Some of the information you may enter on our Web site may be transmitted securely via Secure Sockets Layer SSL, 128 bit encryption services. Pages utilizing this technology will have URLs that start with HTTPS instead of HTTP.Your ConsentBy using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our Web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. In order to view the current Privacy Policy, simply check this section of the website.
Sign up for Tool Experts news
Email
*
Subscribe
Can't subscribe you right now. Try later
Thank you for subscribing to the newsletter! We hope you enjoy shopping at Tool Experts
© 1996 - 2020 Tool Experts. All rights reserved.
Powered by X-Cart
